dzoic.com 2009-12-22

# DZOIC :: Video Sharing Script and Social Networking Script - Youtube Clone - Myspace Clone - Youtube Script - Myspace Script

|   
---  
|  |  |  |  |  |   
---  
DZOIC  
Privacy Policy  
|  | What personally identifiable information is collected from you  
---|---  
 | DZOIC Development collects information in 2 sections of our site. Some personal information is gathered when you register for a demo of DZOIC Handshakes software (although you can use a preset testing account and do not provide your personal/contact information while testing the demo at all). During registration, we ask for your email address. The system will also ask for your first name, last name, and the URL of your web site. This information is used by DZOIC to associate the order of Handshakes script with you and to create a necessary product license key, which will be sent to the email address which you provided during purchase.  
| What cookies are and how they are used  
 | As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Handshakes may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of this web site require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes: (1) Technical administration of the Web site (2) Customer administration (3) Finding problems with our website (technical or content related.)  
| How your information is used  
 | There are 2 reason why we may use your personal information: (1) This information is used to generate and deliver the product license key to you after you complete your order (2) We may contact you later to notify about critical updates of our software  
| Who is collecting your information  
 | When you are asked for personal information on this web site, you are sharing that information with DZOIC Development alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the demo program.  
| With whom your information may be shared  
 | As a general rule, DZOIC Development will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. DZOIC Development may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Use of the DZOIC Development or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the DZOIC Development, other users of the DZOIC Development, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. DZOIC Development may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.  
| What else you should know about your online privacy  
 | Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online through the use of our software demos. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.  
---|---|---|---|---  
Copyright © DZOIC Limited, 2005-2009. All Rights Reserved.
